Again, again, again.
I'll teach you a wacky pose.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
You do it like this. Bleh.
[SQUEALS]
[HUFFING, CRYING]
Not like that
You look like an old guy.
[DANIEL GRUNTS]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
(In Korean) Mom, I can't--
That chambermaid is flirting
with my Daniel!
I don't think he's being
honest with you
about this maid.
Huh?
[CHAIRMAN SONG] (In Korean)
Just find the necklace.
It will lead you to my daughter.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Get her DNA to confirm...
and I'll make you
the youngest CEO of my company.
And Daniel...
No one must know.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
(In Korean) What a pain...
We need to be smart
about this, my dear.
It's not just your man
who's at stake here.
Mom will take care of it.
[DARK MUSIC PLAYING]